# HyungRyul Kim

Email: dev.ryulth@gmail.com Contact: 010-9455-9654

I am a backend developer who wants to create a service that parents can use easily. I enjoy applying technologies that I have not experienced to side projects. Currently, I like Java & Kotlin and Spring Framework. RDB prefers MySQL and NoSQL prefers DynamoDB. Always worry about side effects not happening.

Main technology stack: Java, Kotlin, Spring Framework, MySQL, Docker, DynamoDB

GitHub: https://github.com/Ryulth

Curriculum Vitae: https://ryulth.com/cv-ko.pdf Side Project: https://ryulth.com/side-project-ko.pdf

## Work Experience HYPERCONNECT

Nov 2019 - Present

Full-time, Seoul, Republic of Korea - https://hyperconnect.com/?lang=en

- AZAR API Team Backend Software Engineer Nov 2019
  - Developed azar application server
  - ✓ Develop azar application feature (70million match request per one day)
  - ✓ Trouble shooting
  - ✓ Legacy code refactoring
  - Build micro service
  - ✓ Architecture design
  - ✓ Developed common module
  - ✓ Manage micro service system
- AZAR Match Squad Team Backend Software Engineer Mar 2020
  - Azar Card Match User Experience Enhancement Organization Developer

NHN

Jan 2019 - June 2019

Intern, Pangyo, Republic of Korea - https://www.nhn.com/en/index.nhn

- Dooray R&D Team Backend Software Engineer Intern Jan 2019 June 2019
  - Dooray messenger and editor feature development

## **CNTEXTILE**

Freelancer, Seoul, Republic of Korea

• Internal ERP System Developer Oct 2018 - Dec 2018

Education Kyunghee University

Bachelor of Computer Science

Mar 2013 - Feb 2020

Additional Information

## Depromeet

A joint IT club established with the intention of letting designers and programmers work together productively

## **BOAZ**

Korea's first university student association big data association club

## T.G.Wing

Kyunghee University, Department of Computer Engineering, Academic Club 2016 Club President

Grand Prize at KyungHee University Hackatho

Nov 2018

n KHUTHON (2nd)

Excellence Award at KyungHee University Alg

May 2017

orithm Competition (3rd)

Competition Bronze at KyungHee University Al

May 2014

gorithm Competition (3rd)

Languages Korean

Native

**English** 

Conversational

• OPIC September 09, 2019

**INTERMEDIATE MID 2**